Hello friends, here III Lord has
disclosed its numbers for the third quarter.
So let's see what the numbers were.
All the figures here are in lakhs.
If we talk about its total
income, it is seen to be Rs 5,882 crore,
which was around Rs 5,000 crore in the same period last year
and Rs
5,850 crore in the last quarter. So, if we look at it year after year,
we are seeing a significant increase year after year, we can
say that there is an
increase of around 18 percent in its total income.
And if we look at it quarter after quarter,
we are seeing a completely flat growth quarter after quarter, which is less than 1 percent, which is an
increase of revenue. If we
look at the quarter after quarter, then if we talk about the total expenses, then
we are seeing a total expenditure of Rs 5,197
crore, which was Rs
4,588 crore in the same period last year and Rs 5,186 crore in the last quarter. So,
here we are seeing expenses also
under control.  Regarding
total profit, this quarter has
generated a profit of Rs 724 crore, which
was Rs 431 crore in the last same period and Rs
693 crore in the last quarter. So, if we
look at it year on year, we are seeing good growth year on year. We
can approximately say that we are
seeing growth of around 67 percent
and if we talk about quarter on quarter, then
quarter on quarter we are
seeing growth of around 5 percent, so there are
good results. If we
talk about estimation, then the
estimation of the company by Bloomberg was
around Rs 5500-5572 crore. Here,
from the revenue point of view, it is Rs
5882 crore, which means
we are seeing results beating the estimation here.
And if we talk about Pat,
in Pat,
we were seeing estimates of around Rs 635 crore, so from that
we have seen around Rs 724 crore here.
Whatever has come out, good
results are being seen here,
so these were the numbers of ICICI for quarter three, these are
very good numbers and
if we talk about the
reaction of the market here, then
we can get a good reaction from the market here,
if we talk about EPS, then
EPS is being seen around ₹1 14.48 paise,
which
was 8.73 paise in the same period last year and
88 paise in the last quarter, so here
we are seeing a good increase in EPS,
year after year and quarter on
quarter also EPS has been seen increasing,
so these were the
numbers of quarter three of ICICI, how did you like the numbers here,
do tell us by commenting, if you liked the video then
like and subscribe,
thank you